riversideparkhotel.com 2015-03-08

# Privacy Policy Of The Riverside Park Hotel Enniscorthy

Your privacy is important to Great National Hotels and Resorts. This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that Great National collects, and the ways in which Great National uses that personal information.

## Personal information collection

Great National may collect and use the following kinds of personal information:

  * information about your use of this website;
  * information that you provide using for the purpose of registering with the website;
  * information about transactions carried out over this website;
  * information that you provide for the purpose of subscribing to the website services; and
  * any other information that you send to Great National.

## Using personal information

Great National may use your personal information to:

  * administer this website;
  * personalize the website for you;
  * enable your access to and use of the website services;
  * publish information about you on the website;
  * send to you products that you purchase;
  * supply to you services that you purchase;
  * send you statements and invoices;
  * collect payments from you; and
  * send you marketing communications.

Where Great National discloses your personal information to its agents or sub-contractors for these purposes, the agent or sub-contractor in question will be obligated to use that personal information in accordance with the terms of this privacy statement. In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere above, Great National may disclose your personal information to the extent that it is required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings, and in order to establish, exercise or defend its legal rights.

## Securing your data

Great National Hotels will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information. Great National will store all the personal information you provide on its secure servers. Information relating to electronic transactions entered into via this website will be protected by encryption technology.

## Cross-border data transfers

Information that Great National collects may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which Great National operates to enable the use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy. In addition, personal information that you submit for publication on the website will be published on the internet and may be available around the world. You agree to such cross-border transfers of personal information.

## Updating this statement

Great National may update this privacy policy by posting a new version on this website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are familiar with any changes.

## Other websites

This website contains links to other websites. Great National is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third party.

## Cookies Explained

By continuing to use this site you agree for us to set cookies on your computer

**What are Cookies**

Cookies are small text files stored on your device by a web browser (e.g. Internet Explorer) that hold information about your previous visits to our site. On returning to our site this stored information is fed back to us allowing us to offer you a more personal browsing experience. By using our site you consent to cookies being used in accordance with our policy. For more information on cookies, visit www.dataprotection.ie or www.whatarecookies.com

**Why are we telling you this?**

Recent legislation means EU law now requires website operators to ask for permission before using certain kinds of cookies. To ensure you are completely aware of the types of cookies we use and to enable us to continue to bring you the best possible browsing experience, we are giving you a detailed outline of the cookies we use and their unique role in your browsing experience.

**Types of cookies**

Strictly necessary cookies - These cookies enable you to navigate our site and gain full access to its features and secure areas. Without these cookies essential services cannot be provided.

Performance cookies - These cookies remember information about how you and other customers use our website. This gives us vital information such as which pages are visited most often and if customers are receiving error messages from certain pages. The role of these cookies is to allow us to analyse and improve the performance of our website ensuring you receive a consistent look, feel and shopping experience.

Performance cookies (often known as web analytic cookies) don't collect any information that identifies the customer and all information collected is aggregated and therefore anonymous.

Functionality cookies - These cookies remember choices you made on previous visits to our site such as your username, language or region so we can provide enhanced, more personal features. They can also be used to remember changes you've made to text size, fonts and other parts of web pages you can customise. Functionality cookies can also be used to provide services you have previously asked for such as watching videos or commenting on a blog. The information collected by these cookies may be anonymised and they cannot track your browsing activity on other sites.

Targeting or advertising cookies - These cookies are used to deliver adverts more relevant to your personal interests. Alongside this they limit the amount of times you see an advert and measure the effectiveness of adverts. This means you won't keep seeing irrelevant adverts or the same adverts over and over. These cookies are usually placed by advertising networks with the website operator's permission. They remember that you have visited a website and the information is shared with other organisations such as advertisers. . When one of these adverts is presented to you on a site there will be a quick and easy way to click in and opt out of receiving further adverts.

## Managing Cookies

**Can I disable cookies from your website?**

It is possible to stop your browser accepting cookies from particular websites. However, disabling cookies from our site will mean you lose a lot of functionality, which will have a detrimental impact on your browsing experience and mean that you only have limited access to personalised areas of the site. Without access to the information on these cookies it is difficult for us to analyse the performance of our site. This is essential for us to continually improve our service.

**How to block or delete cookies**

We have explained to you what cookies are and what they do, you can delete or disable cookies if you want to. It is possible to block some or all cookies, or even to delete cookies that have already been set; but you need to be aware that you might lose some of the functionality of the website by doing so. If you wish to restrict or block the web browser cookies set on your device, you can do this through your browser settings; the Help function within your browser explains how to change these settings.

You can visit www.aboutcookies.org, which contains comprehensive information on how to manage cookies on a wide variety of desktop browsers.

Cookies are an essential part of how our site works and you will need to have cookies enabled in order to book online. If you don't wish to enable cookies, you'll only be able to browse the site.

**Third Party Cookies**

In some special cases we also use cookies provided by trusted third parties. The following section details which third party cookies you might encounter through this site.

From time to time we test new features and make subtle changes to the way that the site is delivered. When we are still testing new features these cookies may be used to ensure that you receive a consistent experience whilst on the site whilst ensuring we understand which optimisations our usersappreciate the most.

As we sell products it's important for us to understand statistics about how many of the visitors to our site actually make a purchase and as such this is the kind of data that these cookies will track. This is important to you as it means that we can accurately make business predictionsthat allow us to monitor our advertising and product costs to ensure the best possible price.

We also use social media buttons and/or plugins on this site that allow you to connect with your social network in various ways. For these to work the following social media sites including; Facebook, Twitter, YouTube, will set cookies through our site which may be used to enhance your profile on their site or contribute to the data they hold for various purposes outlined in their respective privacy policies.

**More Information**

Hopefully that has clarified things for you if there is something that you aren't sure whether you need or not it's usually safer to leave cookies enabled in case it does interact with one of the features you use on our site. However if you are still looking for more information then you can contact us through one of our preferred contact methods.

Print
